Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Campaign for Governor of Pennsylvania, 1978; IX.
  - Opposition Research, 6.
    - Candidates for Governor
      - Pete Flaherty (D) Candidate Gubernatorial Race, 1978"
        - Flaherty's Platform Positions, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 16)
        - Campaign commercials, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 17)
        - Contributor lists, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 18)
        - Flaherty campaign finances, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 19)
        - Editorials, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 20)
        - Composite of editorials and statements, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 21)
        - "Facts you should know about Pete Flaherty," produced by Democrats for Thornburgh-Scranton, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 22)
        - "The Flaherty Myth," Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 23)
        - Background on Flaherty in preparation for debate, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 24)
        - Articles and clippings regarding Flaherty in preparation for debate, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 25)
        - Campaign statements, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 26)
        - Transcripts of radio and public appearances, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 27)
        - Flaherty's Opinion on the Idea of a Popularly Elected Attorney General, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 28)
        - Eugene Atkinson and Harvey Thieman, Pennsylvania Politicians, and their connections to Flaherty, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Thornburgh Staff Research on Flaherty for Campaign Strategy, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 2)
        - "Statistical Report," by the Pittsburgh Department of Police, 1976-1977 (Box 89, Folder 3)
        - "Toward a Safer Community," Governor's Justice Commission, Allegheny Regional Planning Council, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 4)
        - Report of the Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1956, 1970, 1971, 1972, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 5)
        - "Housing Need and Rehabilitation in Pittsburgh," report by Carnegie Mellon University, School of Urban and Public Affairs, May, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 6)
        - Reports on Pennsylvania Southwest Associations, 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 7)
        - Opposition research binder on Flaherty and Casey, part 1, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 8)
        - Opposition research binder on Flaherty and Casey, part 2, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 9)
        - Opposition research binder on Flaherty and Casey (partial), 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 10)
        - "Sewage System: Plan and Program, City of Pittsburgh," by the Department of City Planning and the Department of Public Works, January, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 11)
        - "Report of the Housing Inadequacies Task Force to the Reappraisal and Development Commission", May 17, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 12)
        - John F. Casey Company and Port Authority of Allegheny County vs. Pete F. Flaherty, Mayor of Pittsburgh, Court of Common Pleas, Docket No. 3676, January 6, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1)
        - John F. Casey Company and Port Authority of Allegheny County vs. Pete F. Flaherty, Mayor of Pittsburgh, Court of Common Pleas, Docket No. 3676, January 6, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 2)
        - "Reorganization Advisory Committee Report to the Pittsburgh Board of Public Education, part 1" (regarding Flaherty and education), October 24, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)
        - "Toward a Living Renaissance: a Report of the Allegheny County Human Service Commission", November, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 4)
        - "The Fiscal Condition of the City of Pittsburgh, 1969-1976" by Michael L. Myers, Research Analyst (Box 90, Folder 5)
        - "1976 Six Year Development Program of the City of Pittsburgh," City of Pittsburgh, Pete Flaherty, Mayor (annotated) (Box 90, Folder 6)
        - "Comprehensive Six-Year Development Program," City of Pittsburgh, Pete Flaherty, Mayor (annotated), 1976 (Box 90, Folder 7)
        - "1977-1982 Proposed Program, City of Pittsburgh," Richard S. Caliguiri, Mayor, August, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 8)
        - "Six Year Development Program, City of Pittsburgh," Richard S. Caliguiri, Mayor, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 9)
        - "A Decade in Retrospect: a Review of Pittsburgh's Fiscal Experience," by the Pennsylvania Economy League, Inc., 1968-1978 (Box 90, Folder 10)
        - "Performance Evaluation Community Development Block Grant Program, City of Pittsburgh," by the Housing Department, Urban League of Pittsburgh, April, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 11)
        - "Bridge Closing Impact Study," by the Port Authority of Allegheny County, June, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 12)
        - "Allegheny County and the City of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: an Investment Research Report," by Butcher and Singer, Inc., 1978 (Box 90, Folder 13)
        - Clippings, 1965-1974 (Box 90, Folder 14-17)
        - Clippings, 1974-November, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 1-18)
      - Robert Butera ( R ) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Campaign brochures, invitations, newsletters and speeches, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 19)
        - Thornburgh's staff research, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 20)
        - Campaign contributions: fiscal disclosure, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 21)
        - Clippings and news service lists, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 22)
        - Opposition research and analyses by Thornburgh Staff, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 1)
        - Summary of information on Robert Butera, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 2)
        - "Butera For Governor" Committee and Campaign Literature, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 3)
        - Biographies, research and clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 4)
        - House of Representatives: bills, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 5)
        - Clippings, 1962-1976 (Box 92, Folder 6-19)
      - Arlen Specter ( R ) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Campaign literature, platform, newsletters, and memos, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence with Thornburgh and Thornburgh's staff memos, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 21)
        - Opposition research by Thornburgh Staff, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 22)
        - Press releases and advertisements, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 23)
        - News service lists and clippings, 1965-1978 (Box 92, Folder 24)
        - Clippings regarding Specter's politics, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 1)
        - Clippings regarding mayoral candidacy, 1969-1970 (Box 93, Folder 2)
        - Clippings, 1968-1978 (Box 93, Folder 3-13)
        - Gubernatorial race: candidate profile and updates, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 14)
        - Gubernatorial primary: clippings, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Henry Hager ( R ) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Biographical material, newsletters, speeches, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 16)
        - News clippings service lists and clippings, January, 1978-May, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 17)
        - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 18-19)
      - David Marston ( R ) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Biographical material, memos and correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 20)
        - News service lists, clippings and editorials, 1976-1978 (Box 93, Folder 21)
        - Clippings, 1972-1978 (Box 94, Folder 1-7)
        - Clippings regarding statements by Marston, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 8)
        - Clippings regarding editorials, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Ernest Kline (D) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Biography and Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 94, Folder 10)
        - Clippings, 1969-1978 (Box 94, Folder 11-17)
      - Robert P. Casey (D) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Speech, brochures, newsletters, news service lists, clippings, 1970-1978 (Box 94, Folder 18)
        - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 19-23)
      - Andrew Watson ( R ) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Alvin Joseph Jacobsen ( R ) Candidate Gubernatorial Primary, 1978"
        - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Candidates for Lieutenant Governor
      - William Scranton, III ( R ) Candidate Lieutenant Governor Race, 1978"
        - Thornburgh's staff research and memos, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 3)
        - Documents for Thornburgh's staff research, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 4)
        - Biographies and brochures, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 5)
        - Platform and campaign material, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 6)
        - News releases, responses and speech drafts, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 7)
        - Filing of primary campaign expenditures and contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 8)
        - Schedules, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 9)
        - Post Gazette editorial board with Casey, October 4, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 10)
        - Briefing for Roy Fox Show with Casey, October 10, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 11)
        - News service lists, clippings, September, 1977-August, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 12)
        - Clippings, September 1, 1978-November 9, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Robert P. Casey (D) Candidate Lieutenant Governor Race, 1978"
        - Research prepared by Nancy Watson, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 14)
        - Scranton/Casey name phenomenon, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 15)
        - Background, clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 16)
        - News service lists and clippings, May 17, 1978-November 4, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 17)
        - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 18)
        - Casey/Scranton clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Politicians
      - H. John Heinz, III "
        - Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - Frank L. Rizzo
        - Clippings and campaign literature, 1975-1978 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - Richard S. Schweiker
        - Clippings and senate newsletters, 1969-1978 (Box 95, Folder 24)
        - Jim Seif application correspondence, December, 1969-January, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 25)
      - Milton J. Shapp
        - Clippings, 1975-1978 (Box 95, Folder 26)
        - Presentation by the Staff of the Senate Minority Appropriations Committee, July 11, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Other Pennsylvania Politicians
      - Peter Atigan, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Al Benedict, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - James Carter, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - William Clinger, Jr., 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - William Coleman, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - John Dellafina, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Charles Dougherty, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Emmet Fitzpatrick, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - George Gekas, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Helen Gillette, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Bill Goodling, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - K. Leroy Irvis, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Donald Jameson, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Wayne Kelly, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - William Klenk, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Franklin Kury, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Thomas Leonard, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Ronald Lench, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - James McGregor, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - William Moorehead, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - W. Crawford, Murdock, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - Gary Myers, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - Thomas Nolan, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 23)
      - Robert Peirce, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 24)
      - Bud Shuster, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 25)
      - William Spingler, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - Richard Sprague, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - Dennis Stevens, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 28)
      - Delores Tucker, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 29)
      - Bob Walker, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 30)
      - Pete Wambach, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 31)
      - Jennifer Wesner, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 32)
      - Faith Whittlesey, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 33)
      - Primary/Republicans: comparison of positions, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 34)
      - Consumer Party, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 35)
      - Socialists Workers Party, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 36)
      - Lieutenant Governor candidates, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 37)
      - Candidates for General Assembly, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 38)
      - Candidates for State Senate, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 39)
      - Candidates for Congress, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 40)
  - Campaign Memoranda and Planning Documents, 7.
    The valuable files grouped here contain materials that Thornburgh kept close at hand during the campaign. They include campaign planning and strategy documents from outside consultants, which are particularly interesting since they date early in 1978 when the campaign was just taking shape. Also notable are the media planning documents from Garth Associates and Bailey, Deardourff, both of whom participated significantly in the campaign media effort. There are name files regarding politicians, polls, and polling results. Significant communication during the campaign and among staff was via memoranda that relate interestingly to campaign planning and organization as well as to other active political figures.
    - Planning Documents
      - Campaign Staff, lists, position descriptions, charts, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Garth Associates to Rick Stafford, research plan and clippings, January 16, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Bailey, Deardourff and Associates, Inc. correspondence to staff, regarding campaign plans, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Eddie Mahe Correspondence to staff and memo: "Thoughts on Organization", 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - 1978 Campaign Plan for Richard L. Thornburgh, Campaign for the Governor of Pennsylvania, Submitted by Eddie Mahe, Jr., February 8, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - POLITICON: Robert J. Colonna, National Direct Mail Services, Inc., correspondence from Colonna to Thornburgh, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - The Agency, correspondence from Harkins and Uhre to Thornburgh, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Larry Dunn, "Proposed Campaign Plan to Elect Governor Thornburgh", 1977 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - V. Lance Tarrance and Associates, "Research Design for 1978 Governor's Race", September, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Patrick H. Caddell, "Working paper on Political Strategy", December 10, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Michael A. Poling, "Suggested Research Approach", September 1, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Time Allocation, memos of Jay Waldman (JCW) and Jim Seif (JMS) to Thornburgh, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Republican National Committee research manuals: opposition research and campaign research techniques, October, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Staff Memoranda
      - From Paul Critchlow, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - From Pat Crawford, July 28, 1978-September 25, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - From Jim Seif (JMS), April 27, 1977-October 22, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - To Jim Seif (JMS) from Thornburgh (RLT), December 7, 1977-August 29, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Waldman memoranda, Primary election, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 18)
      - Waldman memoranda, General election, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 19)
      - Thornburgh binder of memoranda, General election, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 20)
      - From Rick Stafford (RAS), November 25, 1977-June 2, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - To Rick Stafford (RAS) from Thornburgh (RLT), September 20, 1977-September 6, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Rick Stafford (RAS) notes, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - From Thornburgh (RLT) "to file", May 9, 1977-July 24, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - From Thornburgh (RLT) to various staff members, September 6, 1977-September 18, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - To Jay Waldman (JCW) from Thornburgh (RLT), November 30, 1977-June 13, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Regarding Schweiker, October 11, 1977-January 11, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Regarding Specter, October 11, 1977-January 28, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - From other staff members: John Thornburgh (JKT), Murray Dickman (MGD) (polls), John Kelly, Bob Antonelli, John Casey, H. W. Turner, Ginny Thornburgh (VJT), Rodger Morrow, Tom Darr, and Bill Scranton (WWSIII), January 5, 1978-September 14, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Name Files, 8.
    These files contain correspondence, clippings, and other material pertaining to individuals that were of particular interest during the campaign. There is an interesting mix of names from President Carter, to Governors Scranton and Shapp, to Tony Grosso, a racketeer Thornburgh had previously convicted and who now claimed to support his candidacy. Grosso's campaign "participation" was inappropriate and alarming but peculiarly colorful.
    - Bob Butera, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - President Jimmy Carter, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Joseph Cosetti, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Pete Flaherty, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - President Gerald Ford, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Tony Grosso, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Henry Hager, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Senator John Heinz, 1976-1978 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Elsie Hillman, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Jim Knepper, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Bert Lance, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Drew Lewis, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - David Marston, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Judge Frank Montemuro, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Richard Schweiker, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Hugh Scott, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Governor William W. Scranton, Jr., 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - William W. Scranton, III, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Governor Milton J. Shapp, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Jim Thompson, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Other Pennsylvania names, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Philadelphia names, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Committee of Seventy, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - GOP Pennsylvania names, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Dickman Files and Polls, 9.
    These files are those which Murray Dickman (MGD) kept during the campaign. They include polls and polling data, name files, documents relating to the campaign, and election rules and regulations. Even in 1978, polls were a critical component of a successful campaign, which makes these files of particular interest.
    - Campaign and election rules and regulations, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Organization lists, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - V. Lance Tarrance and Associates, "An Overview of Political Attitudes in Pennsylvania", October, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - V. Lance Tarrance and Associates, "Pennsylvania Aggregates, Statewide and Republicans Only", October, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - V. Lance Tarrance and Associates, "Preliminary Cross-tabulation results of Pennsylvania statewide survey", October, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Campaign manual for county coordinator, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 19-20)
    - Butera, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Hager, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Marston, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Specter, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Lieutenant Governor candidates, Scranton and Whittlesey, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Events and clippings, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Republican State Committee: correspondence, minutes, and annotated clippings, 1970-1976 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Republican State Committee: correspondence, minutes, and annotated clippings, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Republican State Committee: correspondence, minutes, and annotated clippings, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Republican State Committee, address lists and information on individuals, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Republican Governor's Association: speeches, newsletters, and articles, 1977-1978 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Teenage Republicans: letters and GOP newsletters (annotated), 1977-1978 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Polls, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Polls, 1976-1977 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphia Mayoral Poll, September, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Primary Polls, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - General Election Polls, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - "Pennsylvania Statewide Analysis," prepared for the Thornburgh-Scranton for Governor Committee by Market Opinion Polls, August-October, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Candidate Thornburgh's Files, 10.
    These files are campaign documents kept by Thornburgh. Most all materials have been marked with red pen, typical of Thornburgh's personal annotating. Naturally, the candidate's own files will have particular interest to researchers, especially his record of election results! Included here are Thornburgh's notes from phone conversations, speech notes, his schedules, research on opposition candidates, and other more "personal" ephemera.
    - Thornburgh Binders
      - Thornburgh (RLT) schedules: Primary, January 31, 1978-May 14, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Thornburgh (RLT) schedules: General, May 31, 1978-election day (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Republican candidates: Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - Contributors, February 21, 1978-November 20, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
      - Thornburgh County files, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Position papers: Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Pete Flaherty opposition research, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 5-6)
      - Policy information, formerly "Promise Binder", December, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Personal Campaign Files
      - Inspirational ideas and quotes, 1884-1978 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - "Constitutional Revision in Pennsylvania," inscribed on January 23, 1978 by George D. Wolf, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - "Constitutional Revision in Pennsylvania," gift in 1978, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - "Key to the Keystone State: Pennsylvania," prepared by League of Women Voters, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - FBI Directorship and Thornburgh, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Articles of interest regarding politics, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - Campaign research, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Notes and information on Campaign '78, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - Transitions, 1977 and 1978, K&L cards, April 1, 1977; January 1, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, memos, advice, Primary and General, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - "Special Issues" correspondence regarding legal issues and cases, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Business cards, 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Thornburgh telephone memoranda, March 28, 1977-October 2, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Thornburgh telephone notes and election results by county, February 27, 1978-November 9, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Thornburgh telephone notes, November 9, 1978-March 30, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Specter and Thornburgh appearances, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Thornburgh notes, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Thornburgh notes, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Endorsements, Primary, January-May, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Endorsements, General, June-November, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Dickman memo regarding Survey, July 18-24, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Pete Flaherty opposition research, negative articles and data, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - Official election results, 1978 Governor's race vs. 1974 Senate race, November 22, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - Election results, unofficial, letters drafted to State Senators and Representatives, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - PA Society event during transition, clippings, December 10, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - 1978 Christmas cards, December, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - MacLeod interview with Thornburgh (UPI), 1979 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Chron Files and News Clippings, 11.